http://www.australian3de.com.au/privacy-policy

Buy Tickets on Eventbrite
Australia's Premier Equestrian Event
18 to 21 November 2021
MenuVisitors2019 MerchSpectator’s GuideThe Marketplace Shopping VillageDiscover South Australia CloseNews and MediaNewsMedia ReleasesEventing Insider BlogMedia Accreditation CloseTicketsGeneral Admission & Grandstand SeatingHospitality Packages CloseCompetitionResults/Start ListsWhat is Eventing?Cross Country Course MapsWorld Cup Jumping CloseAboutWhat is the Aus3de?Honour RollEvent SafetyVolunteersOur SponsorsWhy be a Sponsor? CloseContact
Privacy Policy
The Australian International 3 Day Event is committed to adhering to the latest Australian privacy laws regarding the way we handle your personal information.
We have adopted the Australian Privacy Principles (APPs) contained in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (the Privacy Act). The NPPs govern the way in which we collect, use, disclose, store, secure and dispose of your Personal Information.
A copy of the Australian Privacy Principles may be obtained from the website of The Office of the Australian Information Commissioner at www.oaic.gov.au
The Australian International 3 Day Event respects the privacy of our customers, subscribers and visitors to the website www.australian3de.com.au.
Our aim is to provide you with a clear and transparent intent of our usage of your personal data, a secure technology platform storing this information and to contact you only for legitimate purposes.
HOW WE HANDLE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
The personal information that the Australian International 3 Day Event collects is used for the purpose of delivering your information requirements, fulfilling your product requests and providing you with updates. This information may change from time to time but may include your names, address, phone number, email address, credit card details (where you provide them) and any further information that you volunteer to us.
THIRD PARTIES
Where necessary to fulfil your requested information requirements, we may provide this personal information to our partnering businesses as necessary to complete any transaction or provide any product you have authorised or requested.
The Australian International 3 Day Event does not send unsolicited mail, nor does it sell, in whole or part, the personal information it collects and does not disclose it to other organisations, except as provided above. We use MailChimp as our marketing automation platform which provides automatic opt-out options every time we contact you.
DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
Your Personal Information may be disclosed in a number of circumstances including the following:
Third parties where you consent to the use or disclosure; and
Where required or authorised by law.
SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
Your Personal Information is stored in a manner that reasonably protects it from misuse and loss and from unauthorized access, modification or disclosure.
When your Personal Information is no longer needed for the purpose for which it was obtained, we will take reasonable steps to destroy or permanently de-identify your Personal Information.
ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
You may access the Personal Information we hold about you and to update and/or correct it, subject to certain exceptions. If you wish to access your Personal Information, please contact us in writing.
In order to protect your Personal Information we may require identification from you before releasing the requested information.
MAINTAINING THE QUALITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
It is an important to us that your Personal Information is up to date. We  will  take reasonable steps to make sure that your Personal Information is accurate, complete and up-to-date. If you find that the information we have is not up to date or is inaccurate, please advise us as soon as practicable so we can update our records and ensure we can continue to provide quality services to you.
POLICY UPDATES
This Policy may change from time to time and is available on our website.
PRIVACY POLICY COMPLAINTS AND ENQUIRIES
If you have any queries or complaints about our Privacy Policy please contact us at:
Australian International 3 Day Event
56B King William Rd,
Goodwood SA 5034
Search for:
Stay Informed Sign up to stay on track with the latest news from the Australian International 3 Day Event.
View our latest newsletter
2021 Online Auction Online Auction information coming soon!
2019 Virtual Course Walk View the cross country course
Accommodation Packages with Inflight Travel Book your accommodation, travel and ticket packages today with Inflight Travel.
Charity of Choice: Cancer Council Please support our Charity of Choice and donate to The Cancer Council of SA
